http://www.marketplaceindia.org/category/privacy

Blog
We at MarketPlace: Handwork of India understand that your privacy is important to you. It is important to us, as well, and we make every effort to ensure that your personal information is secure and your privacy is respected.
When you provide personal information in the course of purchasing our products or using our services or website, you tacitly agree to our collection, use and disclosure of this information as set out in the Privacy Policy detailed below.
If you have any additional questions or concerns about it, please feel free to call a Customer Service representative at 800-726-8905 or Contact Us through this website.
What information we may collect
In order to provide the services you request, we may collect personal information such as your first and last name, mailing address, telephone number, email address, text message address, transaction information, credit or debit card information, and birth month. This information may be collected when you make a purchase by mail, online or by phone, or when you sign up for emails or request catalogs or other marketing materials.
If you purchase a gift card for another person, we may also collect personal information concerning the recipient in order to fulfill your request.
We will assume that you have the recipient's permission to use his or her information for this limited purpose.
If you participate in a promotion or survey or make inquiries concerning our merchandise or service, we may also register personal data.
If you are referred to us through a third-party marketing promotion, we receive personal information.
When you save your information with us online or visit our site, we collect information (Cookies).
In addition, for each visitor to the website, our web server automatically collects the following non-personally identifiable information: your Internet service provider's address, the referring URL, and information on the pages you access on our site.
How we may use the personal information we collect
We use your personal information in a variety of ways related to a purchase.
We process, track and fulfill your order using this information, and we can use it to contact you about the status of your order.
We can use it to respond to your inquiries regarding our merchandise or services;
if you consent to join our mailing list, we use your information to send you emails, catalogs or other marketing materials about our merchandise or services.
We might inform you of any contests, sweepstakes and promotions.
We could send you surveys about our merchandise or services.
Currently, we also gather online information about your purchases and shopping activities to improve the content of our website, to enhance your online shopping experience, and to use in future marketing and promotional activities for our website or our catalogs.
We may use personal information to protect the security and integrity of our site.
We may also use your personal information in other ways for which we will provide notice and obtain your consent at the time of collection, to the extent required by law or this privacy policy.
Sharing information with third parties
We may share relevant personal information with companies who provide certain services to us such as shipping, name and address verification, email distribution, and promotions management. We share only that information necessary for these companies to perform their requested services. We may share information with non-affiliated reputable companies
whose products we believe may be of interest to you. We share only first and last names and mailing addresses but not email addresses.
If you would prefer that we not share information with such companies, please indicate so on your order form or call 800-726-8905.
Removing your name from our email list
If you have received an email from MarketPlace, you may respond with the word "unsubscribe" in the subject line. There are also "Unsubscribe" links at the bottom of the emails.
You may also email us anytime, or contact us by phone at 800-726-8905, or via the mail at the following address: MarketPlace: Handwork of India 532 Baltimore Blvd, Suite 409, Westminster, MD 21157.
Please note, however, such requests may take up to 10 business days to process.
Removing your name from our mailing list
To request that we remove your name from our postal mailing lists, please call 800-726-8905. You can also email us anytime, or write to us at the following address P.O Box 365, New Windsor, MD 21776.
Please include your name and mailing address in the message. You may continue to receive some mailings, but you can expect that to cease in 6 to 8 weeks.
Cookies
Our site uses "cookies" which are small data files stored on your computer's hard drive or mobile device when you visit a site. Cookies may be used in a variety of ways to enhance and personalize your online browsing and shopping experience. For instance, cookies allow us to remember what's in your shopping cart, recognize you when you return to our site, track your orders, and monitor and maintain information about your visits. You may set your browser not to accept cookies ("do not track") or to notify you when you receive cookies. If you do not accept cookies, you will need to re-enter your personal information each time you decide to make a purchase online.
Security
We use various technologies and processes to help protect your information. Information such as your credit or debit card account number is transmitted through a secure server using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology.
We will never request your credit card or other personal information by email. If you receive an email that appears to be a request from us for personal information, do not respond as this may be a "phishing" scam designed to steal your information. Never include your credit or debit card number or other sensitive information in an email as it is not a secure means of transmitting information. We will only request such information during secure transactions on our site.
It is your responsibility to safeguard any password you create to access "My Account" and to sign out when your visit is complete.
If you are more comfortable ordering by phone, call our Customer Service Representatives at 800-726-8905, 9 am to 9 pm EST on week-days and 9 am to 5 pm on Saturdays.
Links to other websites
Our site may contain links to sites owned by third parties. Please review the privacy policy of any site you access through our site as we are not responsible for a third party's privacy policy or practices.
Children's Privacy
Our site is not intended for use by children and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that information has been submitted by someone who is under the age of majority in your jurisdiction of residence, we will not use it. The child's parent or guardian should contact us if we have inadvertently collected such personal information and we will delete it from our files.
Policy Changes
If our Privacy Policy changes, we will post the changes to our site. Your continued use of our site will constitute your agreement with our revised Privacy Policy.
Sign up for Email
Be a part of a community of women who are changing the world.
Sign up for email special offers plus news about the women artisans.
Email address
